I'm going to show you how we can mod our DSi XL and play all of our favorite games off
of the SD card.
The first thing we're going to need to do is open up the camera app.
We need to go in the album and see if this John has the Facebook.
I am human.
Mine does, so the next thing we need to do is power down our system and remove the SD card.
Over on our computer, we need to download the DSi, AIO, zip file and extract it.
Insert your SD card into your computer, select everything except for the memory pit folder
and copy it to the root of your SD card.
Now we need to go all the way deep in the private folder on your SD card till we get to the
pit.bin file.
Rename this file and then we need to go back into the memory pit folder.
Now drag the new pit.bin file into the private folder.
Put your SD card back in your DSi and reopen the camera app.
With SD card selected, tap the album icon.
This is going to boot you into the Twilight menu setup.
Just choose your language and your region.
Now that we have Twilight menu installed, we need to add our games.
Back on our computer, we need to create a ROMs folder to drop all of our games in.
And just like that, all of our favorite games are here ready to play from the launcher.
In my opinion, there's no better way to play DS games than on a DSi XL.